and I think that's going to be one of
the biggest kind of challenges for the
new age of software development where
developers who are very familiar with
writing code and and hopefully living as
much time as they can in the IDE to
effectively understanding okay how can I
actually address this problem through
natural language understanding the
higher level Concepts versus the lower
level lines of code that they actually
need to create so it up levels
developers in in their thought process
as to what's important for the
application versus just the specifics of
the implementation so and I think uh s
like the first time we talked about this
idea then I think you said that this
will turn developers into Architects
yeah which I think I like that analogy
like it is a higher level thought maybe
some will take the route of Architects
of this is how I want to describe the
system some might go more the route of
the product manager and maybe there's
sort of other types of titles or
responsibilities that we can't quite
think of yet